onecoach.com 2006-02-09

# OneCoach More Money · More Life

| 

**OneCoach Online Privacy Policy**

**Last Updated** **September 28, 2005**

OneCoach has established this Privacy Policy to explain how it protects and manages the personal information that it collects from you (the client) online.

| 

**1.**

| 

**Consent for Collection, Use and Disclosure**  
  
---|---  
  
Your use of the ONECOACH site and/or your registration for ONECOACH products and services constitute your consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the ONECOACH site. 

ONECOACH may occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When it does, ONECOACH will also revise the "last update” date at the top of this Privacy Policy. ONECOACH may make new uses or disclosures of information collected from clients, such as in connection with an investigation of a breach of an agreement, contravention of laws, an emergency where the life, health or security of an individual is threatened, the collection of a debt or in compliance with the request of a law enforcement agency or a court order, and in such circumstances, ONECOACH will not inform and obtain the consent of the client prior to such change. 

A client may withdraw his or her consent for collection, use and disclosure at any time by sending an email to [unsubscribe](mailto:unsubscribe@onecoach.com). Please note that, if you do, ONECOACH may suspend its provision of products and services to you. 

ONECOACH collects, at the time of your registration and your sign-on to its web site, certain “personal information” (information that personally identifies you) which may include, but is not limited to, your name, email address, home or work address, telephone number, and information about your computer hardware and software ( _e.g._ , IP address, operating system, browser type, domain name, URL, access times, and referring web site addresses). 

ONECOACH has implemented this Privacy Policy to protect personal information received from its clients, and to respond to any inquiries. The Privacy Policy also provides that ONECOACH will use appropriate contractual means to establish a comparable level of protection for personal information which is sent for processing by third parties on ONECOACH's behalf. 

ONECOACH has designated responsibility for your personal information to its Privacy Officer who ensures compliance with the principles in this Privacy Policy. Other ONECOACH individuals may be delegated to act on behalf of the Privacy Officer. 

**3.**

| 

**Purposes for Collecting Personal Information**  
  
---|---  
  
ONECOACH collects and uses personal information for the following Identified Purposes:

(a)  | to understand client needs regarding ONECOACH’s services;  
---|---  
  
(b) | to develop and provide our web site and our products and services for our clients;  
---|---  
  
(c) | to fulfill your requests for products, services or information;   
---|---  
  
(d) | to communicate with clients and site visitors, when necessary, and to inform clients of upgrades, as well as of other products and services available from ONECOACH, its affiliates and third parties;  
---|---  
  
(e) | to allow clients to access limited-entry areas of ONECOACH’s site;  
---|---  
  
(f) | to personalize some of our services and products for you and to deliver targeted advertisements and offers from ONECOACH and third parties;  
---|---  
  
(g) | to bill accounts and maintain payment records;   
---|---  
  
(h) | to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or government request;  
---|---  
  
(i) | to respond to a legitimate claim, or to address our reasonable belief, that you are violating the rights of any third party or any of the agreements or policies that govern your use of the ONECOACH site or any ONECOACH product or service;  
---|---  
  
(j) | to protect the services, products or rights of ONECOACH, including but not limited to the security or integrity of the ONECOACH site; and  
---|---  
  
(k) | to identify and resolve technical problems concerning ONECOACH’s site, products and services.  
---|---  
  
ONECOACH also uses personal information in an aggregate form ( _i.e._ , not individually attributable to you) for its business analysis, operational, marketing and other promotional purposes.

If we hire other companies to provide some products or services on our behalf, then we will only provide those companies the personal information they need for the Identified Purposes, and we will limit their rights to use and further disclose your personal information as appropriate in the course of their work for us.

**4.**

| 

**Limiting the Collection of Personal Information**  
  
---|---  
  
ONECOACH limits its collection of personal information to only that information which is necessary for the Identified Purposes. ONECOACH does not direct its site to, nor does it knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of thirteen.

When you visit the ONECOACH web site, a cookie may be placed on your computer or the cookie may be read if you have visited the ONECOACH site previously. ONECOACH may use cookies to allow ONECOACH to determine which products and services you have already purchased so that ONECOACH does not provide redundant information to you, and, if you are an ONECOACH affiliate, to track ONECOACH sales made to clients referred by you so that you can receive compensation under our affiliate program. If you choose to not have your browser accept cookies from the ONECOACH web site, you may not be able to view all the text on the screens, or to experience a personalised visit, or to subscribe to certain service and product offerings on the ONECOACH site.

**5.**

| 

**Disclosure, Processing and Retention**  
  
---|---  
  
ONECOACH does not sell, rent or disclose your personal information to anyone else, except:

(a) | to someone you have designated to act as your agent, for one or more of the Identified Purposes (listed in Section 3, above);  
---|---  
  
(b) | to ONECOACH’s employees, independent contractors, subsidiaries, affiliates, consultants, business associates, service providers, suppliers and agents, acting on ONECOACH’s behalf for any of the Identified Purposes;  
---|---  
  
(c)  | as necessary if ONECOACH has reason to believe that disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference (either intentionally or unintentionally) with ONECOACH’s rights or property, other users of ONECOACH’s web site, products or services, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities; and  
---|---  
  
(d) | to respond to judicial process and provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law, or otherwise as required by law.   
---|---  
  
In addition, as we continue to develop our business, we or our affiliates may sell or buy other businesses or entities, or we may merge with another company. In such transactions, personal information may be one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the event that ONECOACH or substantially all of its assets are acquired, your personal information may be one of the transferred assets.

Your information may be stored and processed in the United States, or in any other country in which ONECOACH or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities. By using this web site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. 

After your account becomes inactive (that is, if you request to be removed from our database), ONECOACH will keep your personal information in its archives. Your information will then be used only as necessary for tax reasons or to prove ONECOACH’s compliance with any applicable law. 

**6.**

| 

**Accuracy of Personal Information**  
  
---|---  
  
ONECOACH will use reasonable efforts to keep client personal information accurate for the Identified Purposes, and for minimizing the possibility of making inappropriate client decisions based on such information. Clients are responsible for informing ONECOACH about changes to their personal information. You can do this by sending an email to [info](mailto:info@onecoach.com). ONECOACH will use new or updated personal information it receives from clients to update its own records. 

ONECOACH will use commercially reasonable efforts to protect clients’ personal information.

**8.**

| 

**Access to Personal Information**  
  
---|---  
  
ONECOACH will afford you a reasonable opportunity to review the personal information in your file, upon request to the Privacy Officer at [info](mailto:info@onecoach.com) or by writing to:

OneCoach

3525 Del Mar Heights Road, Suite 356

San Diego, CA 92130

858-792-1250

If ONECOACH is not able to provide access to some aspect of a client’s personal information, it will provide reasons for denying access such as; that by doing so would likely reveal personal information about a third party, or that it is confidential commercial information or attorney-client privileged communications, or that the information relates to a breach of an agreement or a contravention of law, or that its disclosure could reasonably be expected to threaten the life or security of another individual.

Clients have the right to request that inaccurate or incomplete information be amended as appropriate, by contacting ONECOACH or the Privacy Officer as described above. ONECOACH will promptly correct such personal information.
